(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, is the winner of the Physics Bowl
the team that has the most fun?
(Leonard:)Okay. Let me try it this way.
You're annoying and no one wants
to play with you anymore.
(Sheldon:)I see.
(Sheldon:)Well, at this point I should inform you
that I intend to form my own team...
(Sheldon:)...and destroy the molecular bonds
that bind your very matter together...
(Sheldon:)...and reduce the resulting
particulate chaos to tears.
(Leonard:)Thanks for the heads up.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome.
(Sheldon:)- One more thing.
- Yes?
(Sheldon:)It's on, bitch.
- So who did he get to be on his team?
- He won't say.
(Leonard:)He just smiles
and eats macaroons out of his Bat-Jar.
(Raj:)He's using psychological warfare.
We must reply in kind.